

# Dominik Maslanka

Product Manager Uniting Technology with Market Demands & Customer Experience.

Valid B work permit (EU Citizen)

English C1, German A2

- d.m.maslanka@gmail.com
- +41 76 5404170
- Basel 4058, Switzerland
   Erlenmattstr. 81

## Experience



# Product Manager - Magnolia International AG December 2021 - Present (2,5 year) - Basel

Led the strategic oversight and **technical development** of core **cloud based SaaS** components at Magnolia, enhancing product scalability and performance in a competitive digital marketplace

- Conducted comprehensive market analysis to strategically position Magnolia's digital platforms at the forefront of composable commerce, driving significant market expansion and user base growth
- Successfully negotiated critical software licensing agreements, securing favorable terms that enhanced the breadth and competitiveness of Magnolia's product offerings.
- Pioneered the architectural cloud transformation and integration of advanced Al technologies within Magnolia's PaaS products, significantly enhancing functionality and user engagement
- Managed complex stakeholder relationships and led cross-regional team collaborations that synchronized product strategies across major global markets, ensuring cohesive and aligned market approaches in EMEA, US and APAC
- Represented Magnolia as a speaker at the 2023 Dev Days conference, showcasing industry leadership and expertise in digital product management

#### Product Lead - TransactionLink.io

July 2021 - December 2021 (6 months) - Warsaw

Led the rapid development and market alignment of TransactionLink.io's Fintech marketplace, achieving **full AISP Polish market coverage** and integration **within three months** via cloud based infrastructure and dedicated APIs, exemplifying strong agile development capabilities

### Product Owner - Cobiro

January 2021 - July 2021 (7 months) - Warsaw

Responsible for payment service system including integrations with Adyen, ChargeBee and **E-commerce web app based on JamStack**.

 Developed and deployed a comprehensive ecommerce and payment integration system for Cobiro, facilitating seamless digital transactions and enhancing platform robustness and user satisfaction

#### Product Owner - Dodax AG/Myworld.com

December 2018 - December 2020 (2 year) Zug, Warsaw

Responsible for managing the strategy and development of a backstage e-commerce management system for 12 brand new e-commerce stores in Europe (MyWorld) and 12 Dodax stores, inc. Japan, USA, and Canada (CMS, Configuration & Content mgmt systems, Customer Service tools)

- Development and roll-out of the CMS that supports the ecommerce platform and GPDR compliant anonymization system along with ElasticSeach engine Integration to support search experience Improvements
- Building Front-End components architecture in compliance with information architecture modeling and best UX patterns
- Successfully Implementing Objective and Key results framework
- Reducing cost per ticket for Customer Service Support by over 20%

#### About me



Dedicated product manager with **7+** years of experience in the industry. Resourceful and works well under the pressure. A motivational leader with a proven ability to help employees stay on task and happy. Successful in meeting deadlines.

My top Gallup's Clifton Strengths are: Input, Individualisation, Learner, Restorative & Responsibility.

### Education



Studied Computer Science

WIT Warsaw school of Information Technology - 2017-2020

#### Msc in Sociology

University of Warsaw, Institute of Sociology - 2012-2017

#### Social Entrepreneurship

Via University College Denmark - 2014-2015

## **Certifications**



Lean Product Manager

Itamar Gilad

## ITIL Foundation v4 PeopleCert (ID: GR671188108DM)

PeopleCert (ID: GR671188108DM) Sept 2020

#### Prince2

InProgress (ID: GR633111177DM)
Aug 2018

#### PeopleCert DevOps

PeopleCert (ID: GR680000591DM)
Oct 2020

## Design Thinking SHOPA - Design & Strategy

SHOPA - Design & Strategy
Sept 2019